Hmm.
Oh.
Yeah.
We left the atmosphere, the world was grey The
heavy gravity has finally faded away We were
living in a room with the curtains drawn tight
But out here in the void, there is only the light
The terrestrial sounds are just a buzz in the ear
A static station that we no longer hear The
silence is turning into a song This is the orbit
where we belong And we are seeing The true
spectrum A billion stars burning Ultraviolet
and blue Dancing in the dust of a cosmic summer
The nebula Is splitting the dark in two This is
the electric color
The universe waking up for you
They wanted a painted sky A plastic sun A little
radio hit when the day was done But you cannot
capture the burning of a star When you keep the
engine locked inside a jar
Recharging the coordinates they couldn't see
Out here in the quiet of the zero G The
terrestrial sounds are just a buzz in the ear
A static station that we no longer hear The
silence is turning into a song
And we are seeing the true spectrum A billion
stars burning ultraviolet and blue Dancing in
the dust of a cosmic summer The nebula is
splitting the dark in two This is the electric
color
The universe waking up for you.
♪
The true spectrum
Ultraviolet and blue
We finally found the color
so so